(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Why did you have to join
the Black Blood Gang?
I joined the gang
not to save myself.
I joined them
to protect our friends...
Matt is one lucky guy
to have a friend like you.
I want to be as lucky as him one day.
Aren't you curious
why Raze has been quiet lately?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Stay away from Supremo
or you die.
I'm not going to let you or
Supremo's stupidity ruin everything!
The night you and your friend got poisoned.
I kept something from you.
A student requested it from me.
A student you know well.
Jerome
where were you that time?
Zein!
You’re too much!
Isn't it the perfect timing?
You took the liquor and the ice
and came back
and all of the sudden we're poisoned?
Am I right?
But wait
you weren't alone, were you?
Someone was with you.
Do you remember?
Do any of you remember?
What are you saying?
Jerome
where were you that night?
What did you do?
What are you saying, Zein?
Do you remember?
Where were you that night?
What did you do?
You don't want to talk?
You requested it, didn't you?
Can you remember now?
You requested the poison we ingested.
Admit it!
- You poisoned us!
- You're right!
I placed the ice!
I did that because she warned me
that Madam Violet will harm you!
Who's she?
Huh?
Who is it?
Who told you, Jerome?
The student
with the red hood.
The one who helped us in the clinic.
To help Zein and Dave.
She told me that Francisco
and Madam Violet
were planning to poison Zein.
We weren't sure how or when
but we had a hunch that they'll
do it during the acquaintane party.
We needed to act fast.
I know it sounds crazy.
But we needed to poison
Zein with a less fatal dose.
That was the only way to save her
without drawing suspicion
from Madam Violet.
The only way to protect
her was to strike first.
Where's the antidote?
Please take care of her.
I placed the poison inside the
ice to lessen the potency.
But I didn't expect that she
would drink so much that night.
Zein.
Now, let her drink the antidote.
I promise I didn't know
it would turn out that bad.
Even Dave got poisoned.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, okay?
Sorry.
I screwed up, okay!
You're an asshole!
Aren't we your friends?
- Why didn't you tell us?
- Matt, enough!
- Matt!
- Stop it!
Matt, stop!
Stop it, bro.
Matt!
Asshole.
You should be the
one to understand
if Jerome had a secret
he was protecting.
So...
I wasn't the target.
The bottle
someone tossed it to us, right?
The girl.
Is that so...
we have someone on our side
we know nothing about.
Incineration protocol.
Can I sit here?
So much for asking.
You really don't know
how to be afraid, do you?
Why should I be afraid of you, Frtizy?
As expected
from a secretary spoiled by Supremo.
What the hell do you want, Fritzy?
There a few things I want to clarify.
Please.
I don't have time for your nonsense.
Even if it's for Supremo's sake?
What do you really want to say, Frtizy?
Look...
I was a bitch to you before
because I was testing you.
But believe it or not
we want the same thing.
And that's protecting Supremo.
How do I know if I could trust you?
I believe that he's the only hope
for all of us to escape this place.
Yes.
I know I was a bitch to you sometimes.
Sometimes?
But I also want to get
out of this hellhole.
So...
let's work together.
Fine.
But you need to respect
my position as SSG Secretary.
Enough with you bullshit.
Fine.
Just make sure that you'll use
your position to your advantage.
Of course.
But just so you know
this doesn't mean that we're friends.
We just have a deal.
Deal!
Lunch?
There's a policy here
gorgeous first.
So...
wait behind me.
Remember
we're not supposed to
be seen as friends.
Chill.
I'm just getting a drink.
I'm not planning to stay.
Duh!
A queen?
I have a feeling that my bag will fall
and will leave a mess on the floor.
I knew it!
My intuition is so strong, isn't it?
Pick it up for me.
Zein.
This makes me so happy.
My slaves instantly multiplied!
As they should
I'm the queen of this school anyway.
I'm feeling something else coming.
Wow.
Don't you feel
that a hand is going to smack
that foundation filled face of yours?
I see where Zein gets her audacity from.
And you are?
Oh
You don’t have to know me.
And I don’t care about you anyway.
How dare you...
Oops.
Sorry.
I couldn't help it.
Let's go, Zein.
Get out of the way!
Move!
Deserve.
Nice one, Mia.
We should've slapped
her on each cheek.
You take the left and
I'll take the right.
At least you landed one on her.
Way to show her you
can't be bossed around.
But I think I slapped her too hard.
She deserved it!
What if she takes revenge
on you, Mia?
And does more something worse?
Then I'll slap her again.
On the other side of her cheek.
To even it out.
Mia.
Mia's gotten a lot braver.
Don't worry about me, Zein.
I can handle myself.
Mia has grown so much.
Version 2.0!
- Yeah!
- Stop it.
Nice one, Mia.
May I sit?
Let's go, guys.
Let's go?
We still have class.
- Right? Class?
- Yeah, let's go.
- Oh right class.
- Class.
We don't want to be late so.
We’ll go now, Zein. Bye bye.
Bye, Zein!
How about you, Angelica?
Do you want to walk with us?
Come on! Give me your bag.
Let's go.
You're still not eating enough?
What do you call this?
It's food, isn't it?
That's food?
Obviously.
You should try it.
Am I an animal?
You don't eat vegetables?
You're going to make me eat
bermuda grass?
And
what is this?
Bitter melon.
That sounds bad.
Stop acting like a spoiled kid.
What?
No, I'm not.
Grown men eat vegetables.
And what is your scientific
explanation for that?
Scientific explanation, really?
Just try it!
You're not going to get
full if you just stare at me
or my food.
But I feel like
your gaze is enough
to keep me full.
Are you going to eat
or should I feed you?
Why not?
I'm a spoiled kid after all.
You wish.
Just try it.
Come on.
I got my hope's up in you feeding me.
Are you going to eat
or else...
Or else what?
Zein.
Zein?
It's so good.
You should try it.
Come on.
Bitter melon.
It's yummy!
This tastes horrible.
Don't spit it out!
Very good.
Try this one.
You already know what this is called.
- What is it?
- Spinach.
Correct.
Try it.
I don't eat spinach.
Just try it.
One bite.
Promise
it's not bitter.
Try it.
Oh?
Ace...
Huh?
Are you okay?
Supremo
are you okay?
Thank you for the lunch.
Zein.
Are you...
allergic to spinach?
Why didn't you tell me!
Supremo.
It's okay.
Zein
it tastes good.
Just like what you said.
Supremo...
I could never
waste your efforts.
Even if my body refuses.
Please...
please!
Please drink!
Help!
Help us!
Please!
- Help us!
- What happened?
Supremo...
Help!
Let's take him to the clinic, please!
Supremo, please!
Please, help us!
Please help us!
Nurse Cha, please!
- What happened?
- It's Supremo.
He...
He ate spinach and had
a sudden allergic reaction.
Let him lie down.
Now!
Is he...
Is he.
Is he going to.
To live?
Of course he is!
You're going to be okay.
He's stable now.
He needs further observation.
Stupid!
You put Supremo in danger!
I didn't mean to.
You're such an idiot!
Stupid!
Can't you do anything right?
Idiot!
Stop it!
Angel!
You wouldn’t like it if Supremo
knew you slapped his secretary!
I'm sure Supremo will punish
her personally when he wakes up.
She's lucky if he doesn't kill her.
Are you making us laugh?
Do you really think.
Supremo can hurt her?
I think it's you who should be nervous.
If Supremo doesn't want to punish her.
I will.
I'll make sure she gets what she deserves.
Don't worry about her.
You didn't mean to hurt him.
This is negligence, Zein!
You endangered the council!
How could you be so careless!
Ms. Kath, I didn't mean to.
Still!
You were so careless!
Can you use that brain
of yours for once!
Ms. Kath
can we all be just calm?
This is not the time
to point fingers.
Let's just have Supremo
take a rest, please.
We heard what happened.
How is Supremo?
He’s still unconscious.
How about you?
Are you okay?
It's my fault.
If I didn't push him to eat vegetables
this would have not happened.
You didn't know he
was allergic to spinach.
It was an accident.
Mia's right.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Supremo will be okay.
You!
Venomancer!
You need to pay for
what you did to Supremo.
What's happening here?
This is no longer your business,
ex-secretary.
Are you stirring up trouble again?
Our Supremo is unconscious
because of this girl.
He almost died!
What?
I didn't mean to.
Don't play dumb.
You did it on purpose!
No!
I can never hurt Supremo!
Really?
We see right through you!
Are you going to allow
this girl to kill our Supremo?
No!
What should we do to her?
Tie her up and punish her!
Right!
Tie her up!
- Zein!
- Don't you dare touch her!
She didn't do it on purpose!
Stop it, guys!
- Let go of me!
- No!
Get over here!
Stop!
Stop resisting!
Let her go.
Zein!
- Zein!
- Let her go, please!
- No! Zein!
- Zein!
Hit her again!
Let me go!
- No!
- Zein!
Zein!
Hold her and don't let her go!
No! Zein!
Zein!
Your turn.
Haven't we had enough?
Are you serious, Roxane?
She needs to be punished!
Just think of what she did to Supremo.
She deserves this!
Go!
More!
Zein!
Stop it!
More!
Give me that!
You're too weak!
Angelica, stop this!
She's had enough!
Angelica, stop it!
Angelica!
Stop it!
That's what you get
for hurting Supremo!
Should I continue?
- Yes!
- Zein!
Zein!
Stop i! Zein!
Angelica!
Stop!
Please, stop it!
Zein!
What should we do?
Goodbye, Zein Shion.
Zein!
What do you think you're doing?
Untie her!
All of you!
Take my command!
Nobody leaves this hall.
This is an order
from the highest Supreme
Student Government President.
Understood?
Let go!
Zein.
Zein...
Hang in there, Zein.
Nurse, what's her blood type?
I don't know.
Extracting blood sample.
Guys...
we heard what happened.
Are you okay?
We're okay
but Zein isn't.
How did it come to that?
Why didn't she fight back?
I think she has a reason.
But right now let's just
hope she'll be okay.
She’ll be okay.
She's with Supremo.
Can't we go to her?
She needs us.
We can't leave.
We can't disobey Supremo's command.
Let's just wait.
Fine.
I promise you.
They will pay for what they did.
You are such a disappointment.
This is your last chance, Supremo!
Do what you want.
I found the source of my happiness
and I'm not going to let it go.
You're exacty like Lux.
Fragile.
Weak.
I'm not Lux.
Are you sure?
Unlike him.
I'm watching my back.
Let's see about that.
Do you think
I'll let you repeat what
you did before?
You're dead wrong.
Try to touch Zein
and you'll feel what
the real hell is like.
Are you trying to scare me?
No.
But if you're planning to hurt her
you should be afraid.
If you say so.
What the fuck, Roxane.
- We need to avenge Zein.
- What are you so afraid of?
- I wonder.
- Aren't you the queen?
How is she?
- She won't stop so we need...
- to finish this.
- She's gonna be fine.
As long as she's with Supremo
she'll be taken care of.
Stop it!
I'm done with you.
Watch your words, Roxane.
Why?
Isn't this your plan?
Right?
You want Zein dead
so you can have
Supremo all for yourself!
How dare you?
I’m the Queen here!
You bitch.
You think you can fight me?
You bitch!
Really? You're done with me?
No one's going to stop me.
You bitch!
The BBG...
It's about time they stop fighting.
Why did you anger him?
If you only saw how
angry Supremo was earlier
you should be afraid.
It's Raze...
What the...
Devil God Warrior?
Raze.
Please Raze.
You have to help me.
Please.
Sorry...
but I can't do anything about this.
What?
Huh?
Supremo?
Get back.
Supremo...
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Forgive me, please.
Supremo.
I am not asking you to apologize.
Forgive me, please.
I just want you to pay
for the consequences.
Consequences?
Or you're just angry
because your favorite
secretary got hurt?
Huh?
I'm Supremo's favorite secretary.
Don't butt it.
Supremo never had your back.
Every student involved in
the commotion eariler
step to the front!
Who are you to do this to us?
I am the Queen here!
Not anymore!
What the fuck.
What is he doing?
Who'll be the next queen?
Huh?
Queen?
Starting today
there will be no queen from DGW!
I am giving the
crown to Zein Shion.
To Zein?
As the new queen of Hell University.
Zein?
Really?
Zein is the new queen
of Hell University?
You can’t do that!
Of course I can!
And I also declare
Matthew Hart
as the new King of Hell University.
Matt?
SUBS TO FOLOW ONCE ADR IS PLACED
And I have the newest
list of the Highest Ten.
Vice Onel!
Top 1:
Supremo, Ace Craige.
Oh my god.
The leaders of Devil God Warrior
and Black Blood Gang bowed down to him.
Is Supremo really that powerful?
Top 2:
Raze Silvenia.
Top 3:
Nazzer Lumia.
Top 4:
Zein Shion.
SUBS TO FOLLOW ONCE ADR IS PLACED
Zein?
Top 5:
Onel Ty.
Top 6:
Liam Rivera.
SUBS TO FOLLOW ONCE ADR IS PLACED
Top 7:
Matthew Hart
Matthew?
You're in, bro!
I hope we get in too.
Top 8:
Fritzy Saldivar.
I will devote myself to Zein Shion.
Imagine
she's still a newbie
she immediately
got into the ranks.
And on top of all that.
She's even the
queen of Hell University.
Top 9:
Nicky Colt.
Good job.
Top 10:
Jerome Marquez
Jerome?
Me?
Jerome, it's you.
Nice one, bro.
Congrats!
Let's go!
Proud of you.
Thank you, Vice Onel.
Now...
Listen,
Black Blood Gang and Devil God Warrior.
Memorize these faces!
Next week
they’ll be your target.
And I don't care if you do it
during the morning or during Bloody Night.
You're not allowed to target anyone else
besides the faces you see in this room.
Do as you please.
If you want to kill them, go ahead.
Happy hunting!
This is your punishment
and this is an order
from the highest Supreme
Student Government.
Dismissed!
Nazzer!
What's your problem?
Stop him.
Move!
Were you aware of this?
Of course not.
What's your problem?
Why was I kicked out of the top ten?
Huh?
Why do you think so?
Can you stop the bullshit?
I don't have time for this.
Were you involved in my demotion?
You know what, Luke
this is the very reason why you
were demoted from the top ten.
You're too hot tempered.
For once,
calm down
and try reflecting on
your fucking actions
instead of blaming it
on someone else.
Says who?
You are becoming a liablity to the gang.
So if I were you
straighten up.
If you still want to be in this gang.
Good job, man.
We're in the top ten!
What is it?
Are you okay?
There's something you
guys aren't telling us.
Huh?
Matt
tell us the truth.
Did you and Jerome
join one of the gangs
here in Hell University?
What?
Are you serious, Van?
Yeah, right.
That's nonsense.
Okay.
How about this...
how did you guys end
up in the top ten?
And you?
King of Hell University, really?
Is Vanessa telling the truth?
That's not true!
Why would we join the gangs?
Maybe you're forgetting
how many times they've
tried to kill us.
Right?
Exactly.
And if we really did join BBG or DGW
shouldn't we be dead by now?
Exactly.
So how did you manage
to join the top ten?
Our grades are high.
Right?
This is still a school after all.
And can we please just focus on Zein.
She needs us.
I really hope you're telling the truth.
Stop this.
Guys, let's talk about
it some other time.
We should go to Zein.
I agree.
Let's go.
Zein.
Supremo…
You're awake!
What happened to me?
I thought...
No...
I'm sorry.
They targeted you because of me.
You scared me.
I thought I was going to lose you.
Are you sure you're okay?
You're all better now?
As long as you're okay.
I'm fine.
Supremo
why do you look so handsome?
Really?
I thought that
Matthew is the only
handsome one in your eyes.
You look different now.
I admit it, Zein.
I’m not the noblest man
to walk this place.
I've done a lot of bad things.
I know I have blood on my hands
that I can never wash off.
And I'm not proud of it.
But when it comes to you.
I won't have second thoughts.
So I will leave you a promise…
I will keep you safe.
No matter what.
But
we're here in Hell University.
Nothing here is safe.
Well there's actually one.
Where?
Not where…
As long as I'm breathing
you're safe.
I
Ace Craige
will be your shield
your bulletproof vest
and your knight.
Why do you look unhappy?
I'm happy
but
what did you do?
Do you trust me?
What did you do?
Impossible…
Roxanne isn't the
queen of HU anymore.
It's you...
Zein.
It's crucial that Supremo
isn't involved with anyone.
The President must not show
any signs of weakness.
I'm curious of the people's reactions
once they find out Supremo's favoritism.
MkvDrama.net